

#### **CREATIVE STUDIO DIRECTOR**

Singapore PR | Creative Problem Solver | Data-driven Design | Digital Marketing

## **ABOUT**

**EXPERIENCE** 

**EDUCATION** 

**SKILLS** 

Click to navigate!

#### Let's have a chat.

linh.ha1409@gmail.com (+65) 90994109 fuulin.github.io







## ABOUT

**Xin chào**! My name is Linh and I often introduce myself as a "Creative Problem Solver". I have spent 8+ years utilizing my design thinking skills and design sensibility to solve colleagues, partners and clients' problems - be it creative performance optimization, insight collection, project management, or process optimization.



I spent the majority of those years in the Creative team of Advertising companies - in Criteo as a Creative Designer, then Remerge as a Senior Creative Designer and Creative Studio Director. My role grew as I acquired more knowledge about the ins and outs of creatives, both in performance marketing and branding. I have participated in and led multiple impactful projects that changed the team's workflow, implemented new tools, formed creative and A/B testing frameworks. My role recently involved people management and hiring, and I'm ready for new challenges.

In my own time, I love spending time with my 2 daughters, doing arts-and-crafts and playing VR games.

If you'd like to find out more, I'd love to have a chat over a coffee (virtual or real).

Cheers,





#### **CREATIVE STUDIO DIRECTOR**

Singapore PR | Creative Problem Solver | Data-driven Design | Digital Marketing

#### **ABOUT**

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **EDUCATION**

#### **SKILLS**

#### Let's have a chat.

linh.ha1409@gmail.com (+65) 90994109 fuulin.github.io







## EXPERIENCE

# Creative Studio Director Singapore / Senior Creative Designer Remerge (Singapore)

2019 - PRESENT

- · Consulted 20+ clients in the APAC region and globally, notably Nike, Grab, Shopee
- $\cdot$  Participated in / managed projects: developing a creative framework, defining SLA, implementing new tool to expand creative capabilities, defining processes for consultation, systematic A/B testing and creative reviews
- · Managed the Singapore Creative Studio; assited in hiring various roles: creative designer, brand designer, UX designer, project manager

# Creative Designer Criteo (Singapore)

2017 - 2019

- Gathered insights to improve creative performance from analyzing metrics & A/B tests
- · Organized training sessions for internal teams on creative topics
- · Participate in projects and competitions to help boost efficiency and service quality

#### Freelancer

2014 - 2017

- · Various web design, branding, motion graphic, 2D/3D animation, UI design, game development projects
- · Interned at SUTD Game Lab as a Game Artist



#### **CREATIVE STUDIO DIRECTOR**

Singapore PR | Creative Problem Solver | Data-driven Design | Digital Marketing

#### **ABOUT**

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **EDUCATION**

#### **SKILLS**

#### Let's have a chat.

linh.ha1409@gmail.com (+65) 90994109 fuulin.github.io







#### **EDUCATION**

## Nanyang Technological University, Singapore Hons Bachelor of Fine Arts (BFA), Interactive Media

2010 – 2014

- · Grade: 2nd Upper Honours
- Took various creative and skill-oriented courses: Drawn animation, Digital painting, Narratives for new media, Visual communication, Interactive web experience, Game design workshop, Graphic storytelling, 3D Production, 3D Modelling.
- Developed various creative projects as part of the curriculum, both collaboratively and individually.

#### Le Hong Phong High School for the Gifted, Vietnam

2006 - 2009



## **CREATIVE STUDIO DIRECTOR**

Singapore PR | Creative Problem Solver | Data-driven Design | Digital Marketing

## **ABOUT**

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **EDUCATION**

# **SKILLS**

#### Let's have a chat.

linh.ha1409@gmail.com (+65) 90994109 fuulin.github.io







## **SKILLS**

#### **Technical**

- · Adobe Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, InDesign)
- · HTML5, CSS3, Javascript
- · Sketch, Figma
- · Trello, Jira, Confluence
- Pardot
- · Github
- · Google Slides, Google Sheets

#### **Practical**

- · Project management
- · Liasing with external parties / clients
- · Interviewing, hiring
- · People management
- · Presentation, public speaking
- · Brief proposal, pitching ideas
- · Managing collaboration and relationship between teams